Vod2smi by Blue-Bird™
I still think about the night
your mother and I
had to leave you.
Hopefully, it's not for long,
but I'll call you
when we get settled.
When I have a better
indication of what's going on.
Mommy?
Jellybean.
Daddy and I have
a last-minute business trip...
so Rose is gonna stay with you
for a few days.
No. I don't want you to go.
Ugh. It's gonna be so boring.
I won't be able to keep my...
eyes...
Goodbye, sweetheart.
All right, we'll see you soon.
Okay.
Janet, we gotta go.
I wish we could have
put down our bags...
tucked you back into your bed...
but too many lives
were at stake.
Oh, my God.
They've already launched.
We have to stop it.
Come on.
To disarm the missile,
we had to get inside it...
but the plating was too thick.
The only way in was to shrink
between the molecules.
I can't get through.
Hank.
We both knew
that if you go that small...
there is no coming back.
It should have been me,
but my regulator was damaged.
Your mother's wasn't.
Tell Hope I love her.
She turned it off.
Janet. No!
She went subatomic
to deactivate the bomb.
Your mother saved
thousands of lives that day
knowing she'd be lost
in the quantum realm.
Alone.
Afraid.
Gone forever.
Telling you that she wasn't
coming home...
was the hardest thing
that I ever had to do.
But then Scott showed up.
Or should I say,
broke into our house.
And when he went
to the quantum realm...
and came back.
Everything changed.
I started to wonder...
could your mother
still be alive?
So, I dusted off some old plans.
Dad, what are you saying?
I think it's possible
to bring her back.
Okay. We're in.
Oh, this place is a maze.
Where's that map?
We're definitely close.
- You ready?
- I'm ready, Daddy.
Are you sure?
'Cause once we're inside,
you show any hesitation
or fear, we're done.
I eat fear for breakfast.
Wow. That is super cool.
Come on.
Look! It's Anton.
He'll show us the way.
Anton, which way do we go?
Thanks, Anton!
Look, the ants have burrowed
into the tech facility.
Oh no, lasers!
Oh! I think I got lased!
The secret vault.
Tell me you brought
the contact lens.
Yup.
Perfect! Right there.
There!
It's the micro-treasure!
My trophy?
It looks like treasure.
Oh, it is to me.
I want to take it
to show-and-tell.
Oh, no, you can't do that.
You can't. It never leaves
the house. It's too important.
This is the best birthday
present you ever got me.
I'm so touched you think
I'm the world's
greatest grandma.
It was the only one they had.
It makes me want
to knit you a sweater.
Oh, no, the fuzz!
Hey, Scotty...
I was looking at the schematics
for the Karapetyan buildings...
and I think we have
way too many security cameras,
don't we?
No, no, not at all.
I mean, 'cause it's a lot
of security cameras.
I know what he needs.
Who's the security expert
in our business?
You are, but I'm running
the company, right?
And if we overquote him...
he's gonna go somewhere else.
I mean, we gotta land this bird.
He ain't goin' anywhere.
And the expression is
"land this fish."
No, it's "land the bird."
Just like you land the plane.
You gotta land the plane
to be in business.
I know it's silly to get hung up
on these kinds of things,
but I do.
How am I gonna land a fish?
It can't walk.
And if it swam up on shore...
and it battled a hawk,
who's gonna win?
You've really turned me around
on this thing.
It's okay.
We're gonna land Karapetyan.
Now, if you just excuse me...
I'm in the middle of trying to
steal something
with my daughter.
I'm gonna go recheck it.
To the escape ant!
Let's bounce
before the po-po come back!
The po-po?
How do you even know that?
Let's fly, Antoinette!
Let's fly!
Crash landing!
Whoo!
I wish we could shrink for real.
Oh. That is pretty cool.
Hey, I'm headed
to the office, Scotty.
And sorry about freaking out
earlier, you know.
But I feel like I'm way better.
My heart is definitely beating
way too hard and stuff.
And my hands are shaking.
But I think it's unrelated,
you know?
It's gonna be great, Luis!
You got nothing to worry about!
Yeah, yeah. I'm the boss.
I'm the boss.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Daddy!
Come on, Woo!
I've got three days left.
Why would I try to escape?
Sorry, Scott,
but rules are rules.
You trip the perimeter alarm,
we search the place.
Keel to stern, soup to nuts.
Thank you.
It was an accident. My foot
went through the fence.
Our flying ant crashed.
Hey, you try and entertain
a 10-year-old
when you can't leave the house.
You know the lengths
that I've gone to?
Close-up magic.
I learned that.
Why can't you just leave
my daddy alone?
Oh, Cassie.
This must all seem like
a bunch of confusing
grown-up stuff to you, huh?
Well, think of it this way.
Your school has rules, right?
Like, you can't draw
on the walls.
Well, your daddy went to Germany
and drew on the walls
with Captain America.
And that was a violation
of Article 16,
Paragraph Three
of the Sokovia Accords.
Now, as a part of
his joint plea deal...
with Homeland Security
and the German government...
he was allowed to return
to the U.S...
provided he serve two years
under house arrest...
followed by three years
of probation.
And avoid any unauthorized
activities, technology...
or contact with any
former associates who were...
or currently are
in violation of said Accords.
Or any related statutes.
Okay, sweetie?
Wow. You're really great
with kids.
Thanks.
I'm also a youth pastor.
Anyway, not to be
a Johnny ask-a-lot...
but you haven't had any contact
with Hank Pym or Hope Van Dyne,
have you?
- No.
- You sure?
Because it's only a matter of time
before we get 'em.
It was their tech, so they
violated the Accords, too.
And associating with them
breaks your deal.
And, uh, I don't need
to remind you...
that any violation
of your agreement
means 20 years in prison.
Minimum.
I haven't talked to Hank
or Hope in forever.
They hate his guts.
Thanks, peanut.
How'd you do it, Scott?
Do what?
The card trick.
Seriously?
Oh, my God!
You people
can't just show up here
whenever you want
and search the place.
Actually, they can.
You need a warrant.
Actually, they don't.
Really? Wow.
Did you pack your soccer shoes?
- Yeah.
- All right.
Next time I see you will be
on the outside.
All right.
Oh, get on the inside of this.
Hey, three days.
Seriously...
- I'm proud of you, bud.
- Thank you.
You know what?
Give me another one.
Me too!
Gosh! Freedom!
New business!
I am sensing greatness.
I had a fun weekend, Daddy.
Me too, peanut. But just wait
till next weekend.
Once I'm outta here, you and I are
gonna go paint this town red.
We'll have so much ice cream,
we'll never stop puking.
You're gettin' good at that.
How'd you do that?
- Bye, Daddy.
- Bye.
Three days.
Easy-peasy.
♪ Snap your fingers. That gets
them to look over there. ♪
♪ And that is misdirection. ♪
♪ We had a dream ♪
♪ We'd go travelin' together ♪
♪ We'd spread a little lovin'
then we'd keep movin' on ♪
Easy-peasy.
♪ Where are you? ♪
♪ Everything that you know... ♪
♪ Lost... ♪
♪ in the quantum realm. ♪
What?
I'm gonna find you, Jellybean.
I found you!
You always find me, Mommy.
What the hell?
Hey, Hank!
It's been a while.
Um, I don't even know if
this is your number anymore.
And I'm probably the last person
you wanna hear from.
But I just had
a really weird dream.
And I know that doesn't
sound like an emergency
or anything...
but it just felt very real.
I was back
in the quantum realm...
and I think I saw your wife.
And then I was your wife.
I mean, not in a weird way
or anything.
You know, hearing this out loud,
I'm thinking, uh,
it's not an emergency.
I'm sorry to bother you.
I'm sorry for a lot of things.
That means, one tiny atom
in my fingernail could be...
Could be one,
little, tiny universe.
Hope?
Is this another dream?
Do you think it was a dream...
or is it possible that you
really saw my mom down there?
I'm not sure.
I can't be here!
I'm under house arrest!
They won't open while
the system's engaged, Scott.
You have to take me home.
They could show up any second!
Relax. As far as your
nanny cops know,
you're still at home.
Whoa!
Scotty?
He's programmed to
replicate your daily routine.
Nine hours in bed.
Five hours in front of the TV.
Two hours in the bathroom,
whatever that's about.
That's totally inaccurate.
And how do you know
about my daily routine?
Are you spying on me?
We keep tabs on all
security threats, all right?
And so far the biggest one
we've had is you.
I'm sorry about Germany.
They just showed up.
They said it was
a matter of national security.
That Cap needed help, so...
Cap?
Tain America.
Captain. Cap.
It's what we call him.
If you're a friend.
I'm not saying I'm a friend
of... A little, I know him.
He's nice. Whatever.
I'm sorry! All right?
I didn't think I'd get caught.
You didn't think
about a lot of things.
How's Hank?
We're still running. The house
is gone, so is our freedom.
How do you think he is?
I'm sorry.
I know you're mad.
I'm not looking
for an apology, Scott.
The only reason
why we're even talking is...
because we need
what's in your head.
Is this where you're living?
If you need help or money
or something, maybe I can...
We're fine.
Hey, Hank.
Look, I just wanna...
Save it!
- Can we start?
- Yeah.
So, while you were relaxing
at home...
we were building this.
It's a tunnel.
To the quantum realm.
To my mom.
We think she might still
be down there.
We just don't know where.
What?
If we can pinpoint
my mom's location...
then the pod can take me down
to get her.
You built all this
and you don't even know
if she's alive?
It's called a hypothesis.
Last night, we powered up
the tunnel for the first time.
It was overloaded
and it shut down.
But for a split second,
the doorway to the
quantum realm was opened.
And?
And five minutes later,
you called, talking about Mom.
We think
when you were down there,
you may have entangled with her.
Hank, I would never do that.
I respect you too much.
Quantum entanglement, Scott.
We think she might have put
some kind of a message
in your head.
Hopefully, a location.
And opening the tunnel
triggered it.
Your mom put a message
in my head?
Come on. That's insane.
No, Scott.
Insane is going to Germany
without telling us,
and fighting the Avengers.
Just tell me you weren't lying
about the suit you took.
Tell me you really destroyed it.
I did, I destroyed it, I swear.
I can't believe
you destroyed my suit!
That was my life's work!
What was I supposed to do?
You were supposed to not
take my suit!
I'm sorry, Hank!
I'm sorry I took the suit.
I'm sorry
that I called last night.
I don't remember
seeing Janet down there.
I wish that I did.
I just had a dream about her
playing hide-and-seek
with a little girl.
What?
I had a dream.
She was playing hide-and-seek
with a little girl.
Cassie and I do it all the time.
Doesn't mean anything.
But was it Cassie in the dream?
No.
Where was she hiding?
- What?
- The little girl.
Where was she hiding?
Was it in a wardrobe?
No, it was in a tall dresser.
You mean a wardrobe.
Is that what that's called?
What color was it?
Red.
Were there horses on it?
Oh, boy.
It's where I hid
every time that we played.
It doesn't sound like
you really got the gist
of the game.
She's alive.
I knew it.
I knew it!
We need to get that part.
Okay.
The sooner we get
the tunnel working...
the sooner we can get
this message out of his head.
Does Burch have it?
- Yeah. Let's go.
- What part?
Who's Burch?
Wait. What's happening?
We need a component
to stop the tunnel
from overloading again.
I grabbed your clothes.
You might want to change.
Look, I'd really like
to help you...
but if I'm not at home
when they come
to take off my ankle monitor...
then I'm going away forever.
Once we get the component
and power up the tunnel...
we'll get the message,
and have you home by lunch.
We have to hurry.
The entanglement won't last.
You owe us.
All right, fine.
But can I just wait inside?
Because I'm not supposed
to be out here.
Let's go.
- We good?
- Yeah.
I'll be right back.
- Can I have one of these?
- No.
Ah. Susan! Welcome to 'Oui'!
Sonny!
'Oui' is French
for "yes."
As in "yes" to farm-to-table,
"yes" to locally sourced...
and "yes" to planet
before profit.
Well, let's hope
it also means "yes"
to "Do you have the component
I ordered?"
You know, I have always loved
your sense of humor, Susan.
Have a seat.
No, I'm good. Thank you.
Who is this guy?
Sonny Burch. He traffics
in black market technology.
He's been getting us what
we need to build the tunnel.
Could I just have one...
No.
You know, I have
a special friend at the FBI.
And I say "special"...
because, well,
he tells me things
that I didn't previously know.
For example...
your name isn't Susan.
It's Hope Van Dyne.
And your unseen associate,
that's your father, Hank Pym.
- That's not good, Hank.
- No shit.
What do you want?
Relationships
are built on trust, Hope.
And I want our relationship
to have a strong foundation.
Our relationship?
My business landscape
has been shifting, Hope.
Hell, S.H.I.E.L.D. and HYDRA
don't even exist anymore...
but now, Hank Pym...
Hank Pym is a real opportunity.
Do you have a point?
Oh, you think that I don't know
what you've been building
with all this?
Quantum technology.
Now, you can forget nanotech,
forget AI,
forget cryptocurrency.
Quantum energy is the future.
It's the next gold rush.
Is that so?
I want in, Hope.
So, as a gesture of good will,
I have taken the liberty...
of arranging some buyers
for your lab.
Starting bid...
one billion dollars.
Thank you, Sonny, really.
But my father and I
have something
slightly more pressing
than starting a business.
So I'll just take
the component as arranged.
My buyers don't take
no for an answer.
So, we are either
in business together...
or we aren't
in business together.
Then I guess we aren't.
You can go.
But I'm afraid your money's
gonna have to remain.
Let's call it compensation
for my injured feelings.
Listen, Sonny.
This is gonna be
so much easier on everybody
if you just give me
that component.
Darlin', the only thing
you're takin' from here...
is my heart,
but it will mend in time.
Okay.
So, now what?
You'll see.
She said her and her daddy
had something pressing.
- Mmm-hmm.
- I want to know what it is
because if they're not
working with us...
they're working with somebody.
So find out.
I want some names...
Hold on, you gave her wings?
Get her.
Not my turn-of-the-century
chandelier!
Stop firing! Stop!
All right, take this.
Go. Go, go, go!
Go!
Wings and blasters.
So I take it you didn't have
that tech available for me.
No, I did.
It was a pleasure doing
business with you, Sonny.
Oh, our business
isn't finished yet, Hope.
I can assure you of that!
What in the hell is that?
Dad, are you seeing this?
Hope, get out of there!
- I gotta do something.
- Wait!
It is still a work in progress.
You taught me
that kick. Remember?
Yeah, great form.
Those were the days.
Whatever happened to us?
Not the time, Scott.
Damn it, where'd it go?
I've lost it.
I'm not seeing anything
on the ant cams.
Try looking...
Dad?
Give me that.
Now.
- Are you okay?
- No!
He got the lab.
No.
Come on!
What was that?
I don't know.
But we need to find somewhere
to regroup
and figure out where the lab is.
So, where to now?
How about my house? Hmm?
I'm supposed to be there anyway,
and Woo could walk in
any second.
Exactly why we're not going
to your house.
What about your house?
Sorry.
Well, there is one place
I can think of.
No.
No, no, no, no!
No!
Wow, Dr. Pym...
who would've thought that,
once again,
in your hour of need...
that you would turn to us,
you know?
Not me.
Mmm. Help yourself.
Hey, what's up
with the fancy pastry?
We gotta keep
the food budget down.
Well, what are we supposed
to have for breakfast?
The oatmeal packets.
Oatmeal packets.
- It's insult.
- Why is it an insult?
Because it tastes like sand.
You know why?
'Cause it's organic.
It's not organic, it's sand.
It's the most important meal
of the day.
You know what,
you can get creative with it.
Break teeth.
Put a little brown sugar on it.
You can put some cinnamon.
Put a little honey.
Whatever you want...
Guys, guys, guys.
Come on, man.
We got bigger fish to fry.
Is that my desk?
- Yeah.
- What?
Why do I have such a small desk?
Because you weren't there
when we were choosing desks.
You snooze, you lose.
Well, I was under house arrest.
Yeah.
You know what,
this isn't even a desk.
This is garbage.
You found this outside
amongst garbage.
I got it at a rummage sale.
So, you save money on my desk?
Guys.
Hope, please,
we need to focus, all right?
We gotta find
that lab already. Jeez.
Oh, you know what?
I heard stories,
like what happened to you.
This crazy, creepy cat, who
walks through walls and stuff.
Like a ghost.
Like Baba Yaga.
Baba Yaga, the witch.
They tell stories to children
to frighten them.
You know Baba Yaga?
Whoever stole it...
we need to find it.
Oh, you don't find someone
like that. They find you.
Like Baba Yaga.
Dr. Pym, you're the smartest
genius I know.
Didn't you put some kind of
LoJack on your lab?
Because if you didn't,
we have a variety
of affordable options.
Of course I did, Luis.
It was disabled.
Whoever stole the lab knew
exactly what they were doing.
They also looked like
they were phasing.
Phasing?
Quantum phasing.
When an object moves
through different states
of matter.
Oh, yeah,
that's what I was thinking.
The lab emits radiation.
Can we modify a quantum
spectrometer and track it?
That could work, yes, but all
my equipment is in the lab.
Where else can we find
that equipment?
Well, there is one person.
Bill Foster.
Great!
Who's Bill Foster?
He's an old colleague of
my dad's, from S.H.I.E.L.D.
They had a falling out
years ago.
You seem to have a lot of
falling outs with people.
It's probably
just a waste of time.
Hey, I'm risking everything
by being here.
Don't you think we should check?
We need to find out
who took the lab.
Guys, it's not a good idea
to be out in the open like this.
Relax,
no one's gonna recognize us.
What, because of hats
and sunglasses?
That's not a disguise, Hank.
We look like ourselves
at a baseball game.
In an isolated system...
particles co-exist in
a stable phase relationship.
If the system
is interfered with,
that stability becomes chaos.
Unpredictable.
Dangerous.
Beautiful.
Isolated completely,
a quantum system
would revert back to
separate states of matter...
each entangled with a distinct
state of its environment.
In other words,
the object in question
would be both
in and out of phase...
with multiple
parallel realities.
Speaking of being out of phase
with reality.
I am noticing
an unusually high number
of glazed eyes out there
among you.
So, why don't we call it
a few minutes early?
That'll be enough for today.
Thank you, ladies
and gentlemen, you may go.
It's incredible.
You're linked to Janet.
It's quantum entanglement
between the quantum states of
Posner molecules in your brains.
Yeah, that's what
I was thinking.
Do you guys
just put the word "quantum"
in front of everything?
Doctor, we need to find our lab.
Hope, I'd love to help you...
but I don't have anything
like the equipment
you're describing.
I told you this is a waste
of time. Come on, let's go.
Don't condescend, Hank.
You're the one who's
on the run from the FBI.
All because
you had to grow to a size
that finally fit your ego.
That wasn't me in Germany.
It was this idiot.
Really?
Going that big,
it must've been exhausting.
I slept for three days
straight. You have no idea.
Actually, I do.
Back in the day,
I was Hank's partner
on a project called Goliath.
Excuse me?
You were my partner?
The only thing more tiring
than going that big
is putting up
with Hank's bullshit.
Right...
I don't know.
How big did you get?
My record? 21 feet.
- Not bad.
- You?
I don't...
No, really, I'm curious.
- 65 feet. Yeah.
- Whoa!
- Huge.
- 65.
If you two are finished
comparing sizes...
we need to figure out a way
to track down the lab.
And the great Hank Pym hasn't
figured that one out yet?
Strange.
You had all the answers
back in the day.
That's why I left the project.
Left? I fired you.
Best decision I ever made.
Hank was a terrible partner.
Temperamental...
stubborn, impatient.
Sooner or later,
he just pushed everyone away.
Just the mediocrities.
Janet was the only one
who could endure him
and chose to stick it out.
Watch it, Bill.
She paid the price,
though, didn't she?
You son of a bitch.
I didn't come here
to listen to you two squabble.
I'm trying to save my mother.
Now, which office would you say?
Oh, it's Woo.
Someone must have seen me.
Relax.
If this is about you,
they'd be in your house by now.
What are you, 15?
Come on.
We gotta go right now.
Wait. You might be able to
improvise that tracker...
if you modify
the diffraction units
on one of your regulators.
- That could work.
- I don't know what that means.
Thank you. Thank you.
But, Doctor, campus police says
they ID'd both Pym and Van Dyne.
I don't know
what to tell you, Agent.
I haven't talked to Hank
in 30 years.
I can assure you
I'm the last person
he would want to visit.
Oh, come on, you expect us to...
Hey, hey.
Why is that?
Simple.
We hate each other's guts.
So I'm a terrible partner?
Foster, he hasn't had
one good idea
in his unremarkable career.
But his idea about the
diffractors could work, right?
Fine, one decent idea.
Except, I eliminated
the diffractors
when I upgraded the suits.
So, if we had an old suit,
we might be able
to track down the lab?
Yes, but we don't.
- What if we did?
- What do you mean?
I mean...
life's funny.
Oh, my God.
You didn't destroy the suit.
What?
Well, it was
your life's work, Hank.
I couldn't destroy that.
Before I turned myself in,
I shrunk it down
and mailed it to Luis.
You sent my suit
through the mail?
Hey, the postal service
is very reliable.
You know, they do tracking
numbers now. Like UPS.
Where is it?
It's in a very safe place,
all right? Don't worry.
What, the trophy?
No, it's not here.
What do you mean it's not
there? Where could it be?
I looked everywhere.
It's not here.
Hey, get away from the plant.
But I put it back
after Cassie and I...
Show-and-tell.
Scotty?
No, stop!
Well, the good news is
I know where it is.
Whenever you go
back to school...
isn't everything supposed to
look so much smaller?
This place seems huge.
What is it?
It's the new regulator.
Hank, what's
going on with this suit?
How much of
a work in progress is this?
Uh-oh.
No, no, no.
Oh.
What are you, laughing?
Please, could you just...
Okay, okay.
What do you see?
The sizing coils
are malfunctioning.
Just let me...
Ow!
- Sorry.
- It's all right.
Okay. All right.
Try that.
Sorry.
What?
Awesome.
If only Cap could see you now.
Hilarious.
What are we gonna do?
Hey!
Where's your hall pass?
Hey, I'm talking to you.
Hey!
Hey. Eh...
You can do it.
You almost got it.
Oh, peanut.
Okay, let's go.
Hiya, champ,
how was school today?
All right, get your jokes out now.
Can you fix the suit?
So cranky.
You want a juice box
and some string cheese?
Do you really have that?
Let's see if Foster was right.
This has gotta be the lab.
Let's go get it.
Yeah.
This seems right.
Look at us, teaming
up twice in one day.
Makes you think, huh?
About what?
Germany.
What do you mean?
We were working together,
training together...
and other stuffing together.
If I had asked you,
would you have come?
I guess we'll never know.
But I do know one thing.
What?
If I had,
you'd have never been caught.
Hey, Scott.
You think you can stop
daydreaming about my daughter
long enough to get my lab?
- Yes, sir.
- Thank you.
Okay, you're transmitting.
What took you so long?
Sorry, I had to come
up with a name for my ant.
I'm thinking
Ulysses S. Gr-Ant.
You like it?
Hilarious.
I'm not getting anything
on the monitors.
There's some kind of
electronic disturbance.
Be careful.
You know me, Hank.
I'm always careful... Whoa!
It's okay.
It's just the suit.
- How do you know?
- Look.
That's Ghost?
What is she doing?
Do you think that suit is how
she goes through walls
and stuff?
Let's just get outta
here before she wakes up.
Hope,
look! There's the lab.
Now, we're sure
this is our shrunken building
and not somebody else's, right?
Just take it, Scott.
Come on, we gotta be fast.
I'll get it.
Oh, shit...
Hope. Hope! Hank.
Guys.
I don't think they can hear you.
Hi.
I'm Ava.
Scott.
So, you don't need the suit...
to go through things.
No.
It just helps me control it.
And the pain, supposedly.
You're not gonna reach
into my chest
and crush my heart, are you?
You're funny.
I'm not gonna hurt you, Scott,
unless I have to.
I need...
what's in your head.
Let's wake up
the rest of the gang
and get this over with,
shall we?
Get up!
Come on!
Dad?
Don't ever touch him again.
Now, now, Hope...
I think I'm being rather
gentle with your father,
all things considered.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Another casualty
of Hank Pym's ego.
Bill.
What have you done?
It's what you've done,
Dr. Pym.
You're with her?
Oh, man.
I thought you were cool.
What the hell is going on here?
I doubt Hank has
ever mentioned my father.
Why would he?
Elihas Starr.
They were colleagues
at S.H.I.E.L.D.
Quantum research.
Until my father dare disagree
with the great Hank Pym.
You had him fired.
Oh, and discredited
for good measure.
My father tried to continue
his research on his own.
Desperate to restore his name,
so he took risks.
No, no, no!
Too many.
Until something went wrong.
He told us to run.
Elihas, what's happening?
Just go. Go!
Daddy! Daddy!
I could tell he was scared.
Daddy!
Ava, no!
I didn't want him to be alone.
No! No!
When I woke up,
my parents were dead.
I wasn't so lucky.
They call it
"molecular disequilibrium."
A rather dull name, I think.
Doesn't quite do justice
to what it means.
Every cell in my body
is torn apart...
and stitched back together.
Over and over.
Every day.
I was still at S.H.I.E.L.D.
when I got the call
about a quantum anomaly
in Argentina.
Hello, Ava.
My name's Bill.
I was a friend of your father's.
I brought you something.
It's all right.
Try again.
That's it.
Dr. Foster did his best
to keep me safe.
But others at S.H.I.E.L.D.
saw an opportunity
in my affliction.
They built me
a containment suit,
so I could control my phasing.
And trained me
to be a stealth operative.
They weaponized me.
I stole for them.
Spied for them.
Killed for them.
And in exchange for my soul...
they were going to cure me.
They lied.
When S.H.I.E.L.D. collapsed,
I took Ava in.
I built the chamber
to slow her decay,
but her condition
was progressive.
I didn't know how to cure it.
She wanted to kill you, Hank,
but I told her no...
and that she should
watch you instead.
And sure enough, she discovered
that you were
building the tunnel.
Then, she told me about Lang.
And the message from Janet
inside his head,
that's when I...
Christ's sake!
That's me. I'm sorry.
Look, can you tell me
who's texting me?
"Cassie, 911."
That's my daughter.
I need to text her back.
No, that's not happening.
What, it's 911.
That means it's an emergency.
You're not making
demands here, Lang.
You're not appreciating
the gravity of the...
Okay, look, she's trying
to video chat me now.
Something might be wrong.
Let me talk to her. Please.
Cassie, are you okay?
What's the emergency?
I can't find my soccer shoes.
What?
I have a game tomorrow.
Hey, Scott,
I know that they're there.
Can you just walk the phone
around the house?
No, I can't do that right now.
- Why not?
- Because I'm sick.
Hey, can you just
maybe look around
later then and call me back?
Please? Thank you.
Bye, Daddy!
- Bye, peanut!
- Feel better!
Feel better, buddy!
I'm sorry.
It said emergency.
Ava, I want to help you.
She doesn't need your help.
I know how to save her.
Oh, really? How?
Janet.
For the last 30 years,
she's been down there
absorbing quantum energy.
We can extract that energy.
We can use it to repair
Ava's molecular structure...
Extract it?
- Yes.
- Are you insane?
That would rip Janet apart.
You don't know that.
I'm gonna fire up your tunnel.
When Janet's location
pops into Lang's head,
he's gonna give it to me...
or I'm gonna turn him over
to the FBI.
What?
You are gonna stay here...
just in case I need your help.
Like hell I would help you!
You'll do whatever I say.
You're gonna kill Janet!
I'd be more worried
about yourself, Hank.
Goddamn it, Bill!
- Dad?
- Calm down, Hank.
So help me God...
The pills.
It's his heart!
He needs his pills.
Please, Dr. Foster.
They're in the tin. Please.
He could die!
Come on!
Help him!
Dad, just hang on, all right?
Just keep breathing.
Stay calm.
Help him, man! Come on!
The Altoid tin!
Wait!
Thanks, guys.
Hank!
Bill is filling
that girl's head with lies.
Elihas Starr was a traitor.
He stole my plans.
Now, bring it down.
All right, lock it in.
No, no, no.
The bolt is on the other side.
Tighten that one down,
then bring it down one notch.
Good job.
It'll work.
Foster, he could have fried
the entire system.
Look, we'll adjust the relays
while you go reprogram
the settings, all right?
It's going to be fine.
So, this is it.
Yeah. You'd think
with all this time
to prepare I'd be more ready.
Oh, going subatomic isn't
something you can prepare for.
It kind of melts your mind.
I mean seeing my mom again.
Oh.
What if she's a completely
different person?
Yeah, like, uh,
George Washington.
I'm serious, Scott.
Or George Jefferson.
What if she's forgotten
about me?
When I was in prison...
the only thing that got me
through was Cassie.
I could have been locked up
for 100 years...
I never would have
forgotten her.
I know your mom
is counting the minutes
until she can see you again.
Thank you.
Hey.
We got a big problem.
You forgot
the motion sensor lights
on the back of the building.
Oh, no.
And they're on the proposal,
and Karapetyan
asked for them specifically.
Uh, yeah, look,
it's been a little crazy.
Look, maybe I could stop by
tomorrow, take a look at it.
No. No, no, no, no.
The meeting is first thing
in the morning.
You gotta come right now
and fix it.
I can't. I wish I could,
but I can't leave.
You know what,
I'm coming to you.
I'll just bring the plans.
They're on the laptop.
And you can fix them there.
Just tell me
where you are, okay?
It's complicated.
What do you mean
it's complicated?
As you can see, sir,
this system is state of the art.
Security of tomorrow, today.
Oh, that's so good!
And I love the lean-in, bro.
Keep practicin'.
Hey, I just gotta
drive up to Scotty's,
so we can fix the plans.
But don't worry, I'll be back
in plenty of time.
- As you can see...
- Oh, oh, oh!
Tell me you got the van washed
for tomorrow morning.
Down to the undercarriage, baby.
You sprung
for the undercarriage wash?
Well, you said get the works.
That's a scam, bro. We live
in California, not Minnesota.
He's right.
The undercarriage wash,
that's for cleaning
off road salt...
laid down in our
more snow-laden sister states.
Who are you,
and why do you know so much
about car wash protocol?
Well, my name is Sonny Burch.
And I do my research, Luis.
To wit, I have learned
from a friend of mine...
at the FBI that you are
a known associate
of Scott Lang...
a known associate of Hank Pym,
who I've also learned...
has a portable
shrinking laboratory...
filled with
all kinds of juicy tech.
And you're gonna tell me
where it is.
Well, I hate to break it to you,
but I don't know
what you're talking about.
Well, I sense a resistance
in you, Luis.
And I have promised results
to some dangerous people.
So, I'm gonna introduce you
to my good friend, Uzman.
Now...
Uzman is a master
at extracting information
from the unwilling...
through psychoactive means.
Oh, is that truth serum?
There's no such thing
as truth serum.
That's just nonsense from TV.
Well, what is it then?
It's a little concoction
that he's been perfecting
since his days with the S.I.S.
It makes you suggestible
and highly responsive.
Well, dude, that's truth serum.
No, it's not.
No offensing, but they sound
like truth serum to me.
- Right?
- It's not a truth serum.
Okay. Hey, I believe you.
It's not a truth serum.
I mean, if it walk like duck
and talk like ducks...
The truth serum.
Well, I have
a lot of allergies...
so you might wanna think
about that.
We've got to get that lab back.
What?
The chamber and the suit
are barely helping anymore.
How long have I got?
A couple of weeks, maybe.
Well, then we'll make them
bring the lab back.
How?
Lang. He has
a daughter, right?
You can't mean that.
Ava!
I tolerate a lot of the things
you do out there...
but I won't be a part
of anything like that.
You're not the one who's about
to fade away into nothing, Bill.
I am!
You said you could fix me!
You promised.
I know. I will.
But not like that.
You lay one finger
on that little girl...
I won't help you.
And we're done.
Fine.
There are other options.
You know what? You're right.
This isn't truth serum.
Because I don't feel anything.
That was a lie.
I do feel something.
This is truth serum!
There's no such thing!
Okay.
Okay, okay.
Now, I'm gonna make this
real easy for you, Luis.
Okay.
Where is Scott Lang?
Well, see, that's complicated.
Because when I first met
Scotty, he was in a bad place.
And I'm not talkin'
about cell block D.
His wife had just filed for
divorce, and I was, like...
"Damn, homie. She dumped you
when you're on lockup?"
And he was, like,
"Yeah, I know."
"I thought I was gonna be
with her forever..."
"but now I'm all alone."
"And I was, like," Damn, homie.
You know what?
"You gotta chin up, because
you'll find a new partner."
"But you know what? I'm Luis."
And he says,
"You know what? I'm Scotty,"
"and we're gonna be
best friends."
Okay, hold on, hold on.
I like a good story
as much as the next person...
but what in the hell
does this have to do
with where Scott Lang is?
I'm getting there.
You put a dime in him,
you gotta let the whole song
play out.
He like human jukebox.
Oh, my 'abuelita' had a jukebox
in the restaurant!
Yeah, only played Morrissey.
And if anybody ever
complained, she'd be like...
You know, Chicanos,
we call him "Moz."
Then, ¡adios!
What can I say?
We relate to his
melancholy ballads, you know?
- Lang!
- Right, right, right.
So, anyway,
Scotty gets out of jail,
and he starts working for Hank.
That's when he met Hope.
And Hope's all, like...
"I want nothing to do
with you."
"Look at my hairdo,
I'm all business."
And then Scotty's, like,
"You know what, girl?
My heart is all broken."
"And I'll probably
never find love again,"
"but damn
if I want to kiss you!"
But then you fast forward
and they're all
into each other, right?
And then Scotty's, like,
"You know what?
I can't tell you this..."
"but I'm gonna go trash an
airport with Captain America."
"And then she said," I can't
believe you split like that!
"Smell you later, dummy."
So, Scotty goes on house arrest.
And he won't admit it,
but his heart is all, like...
"Damn! I thought
Hope coulda been"
"my new true partner,
but I blew it!"
But fate brought 'em
back together.
And then Hope's heart is all...
"I'm worried
that I can't trust him..."
"and he's gonna screw up
again, and ruin everything!"
And then
my heart is all, like...
"That fancy raspberry filling
represents the company's red"
"and we're days away from
going out of business. Oh!"
"Out of business"?
"Days away"?
Damn truth serum!
I was trying to protect
you guys. I swear to God.
I was trying to be
a good boss, but we're broke!
And the Karapetyan's
our last hope.
And if we don't show up,
we're done!
That's terrible bossing!
Damn, bro!
- That's on me! That's on me!
- Hey!
Enough.
I'm gonna ask you one more time.
Where is Scott Lang?
I've been trying to tell you,
he's in a tricky spot,
emotionally speaking.
Emotionally speaking.
Well, where is Scott Lang,
literally speaking!
Oh! The woods.
The woods?
Baba Yaga!
What do you mean, "the woods"?
The Muir Woods,
the second fire road
off the Panoramic Highway!
For God's sake!
♪ Baba Yaga,
come at night ♪
♪ Little children,
sleepy tight ♪
Damn it!
If that freak gets Pym's tech...
I'm never gonna see it.
So, what do we do now?
It's easier to steal it
from the Feds
than from the boogeyman.
Hey, it's me. How'd you like
to get a promotion?
I got the location on Pym,
Van Dyne and Lang.
But you gonna
have to take 'em down now,
because they ain't gonna
be there for long.
And when you do,
you gonna get me that lab.
Understood.
Good news, gentlemen.
Feds are gonna do
the hard work for us.
What are you lookin' at?
Change my tires!
Right.
- Sir.
- Can you knock?
Sorry, sir.
Uh, but I just got a lead.
Ooh, I love leads.
System's in the green.
Priming the coils.
Full charge.
As soon as the tunnel's open...
let us know if you get anything
that could be
a part of her message.
Yeah, yeah. I will.
Okay, then.
Here it goes.
We did it!
You got anything?
Nothin'.
Well, just give it a minute,
because it could...
No.
No, no, no, no!
What's happening?
It's shutting down.
Maybe our vectors are off.
We've gone over them a million
times, I know they're right!
Then what else could it be?
I don't know!
- Scott, what are you doing?
- Scott, get away from that!
Scott, you can't...
I'm sorry, I don't know
how much time I have.
I need to fix the algorithm.
Trust me,
after 30 years down here...
I've thought about it a lot.
Janet?
Hi, honey.
Jellybean.
Mom?
It's not the reunion
I'd imagined.
It's all so rushed.
You two have done
such great work.
You just need a little...
nudge.
Janet, how is this possible?
It wasn't a message you put
in Scott's head.
It was an antenna.
Clever girl.
I'm so proud of you.
Honey, tell us where you are.
Tell us how to find you.
No, the probability fields
are too complex.
That's why I needed
to talk to you.
You have to follow my voice.
Of course!
Like tracing a call
back to its source!
I'm tracking your signal
using subatomic frequencies...
between point two
and point nine.
I'd narrow it to four and six.
That's too tight.
We could miss you.
Look at us squabbling again.
Fine. All right,
between three and seven.
Our first fight in decades,
and it's over just like that.
Bullseye.
Source lock.
It's you.
We got it!
You have to meet me
at these exact coordinates.
In the wasteland,
beyond the quantum void.
It's very dangerous,
especially on the human mind,
so be careful.
Time and space work very
differently down here.
You have two hours.
After that, the probability
fields will shift...
and it'll be another century
before they align
like this again.
We'll find you.
I know you will, Jellybean.
Nope.
Nothing. I got nothing.
No sign of Janet.
Perfect.
How did we get up here?
All right, first you're gonna
see all kinds of lights...
and it's gonna get
really trippy...
but then it's gonna turn black
and silent. Really silent.
Scott, I'll be fine.
I'm just saying
because I've been down there.
Yeah, so you've mentioned.
Um, sorry.
I have to take this.
Hey, man, you coming?
No, I'm not,
but you know what? Ghost is.
And you know what? The Feds,
they know where you are.
- What?
- I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
Uh, they gave me
some truth serum.
And then all of a sudden
I started talkin' all honestly.
Like, I hate the way
that you load the dishwasher.
I hate it, I hate it.
- Uh...
- But you need to go home...
because the Feds
are probably going there now!
And by the way...
who puts the plates on the top
rack? They don't go there!
I feel like such a jerk.
You're gonna be really mad.
We gotta go now.
What?
Ghost knows where we are.
So does the FBI.
How?
- I told Luis where we are.
- You what?
I told him to come here
so I could help him
with the Karapetyan proposal.
Oh, my God!
Look, we need
to land that account.
Otherwise, we lose the business!
Do you know hard it is
for ex-cons
to find work these days?
Jesus, Scott!
90 seconds to close
the aperture!
You have to depolarize
the coils first!
I know!
I'm really sorry...
but the, um, FBI
is coming to my place so...
I have to go.
Can I borrow the suit?
Gyroscopic stabilizers.
Powering on.
I'm just gonna borrow the suit.
I'll come back.
Just tell me where you'll be.
- Don't bother.
- What?
We'll come
and get the suit from you,
as soon as we've found my mom.
- Hope...
- Scott, just go!
- Scott?
- Daddy?
It's us, buddy!
We're here for Cassie's shoes!
He must be resting.
Honey, why don't you go upstairs
and look under your bed?
Daddy, you upstairs?
Daddy?
What the...
He really lives
like a pig these days.
Daddy?
Spread out!
Again?
You people have no shame!
The monitor says
that he's in the bathroom.
Yeah, I'm not buying it!
Cassie, let the man get by!
But Daddy's super sick!
I'll see about that!
He says he doesn't want
anyone else to get sick!
I'll take my chances, sweetie.
He barfed. Like, a lot.
Young lady, I'm a federal agent.
I've seen worse things
than vomit.
Like, "a lot" a lot?
- Yes!
- Forget it, move aside!
No!
Woo!
- What are you doing here?
- Scott.
I'm sorry, I'm just really sick.
I told you.
Excuse me.
Sometimes you gotta just
get it out. You know?
Sorry.
I'll start the van.
You get the lab.
Freeze!
You're surrounded!
Hank Pym...
Hope Van Dyne...
you're under arrest.
This is harassment!
Actually, it's not.
What does the FBI
even stand for...
"Forever Bothering Individuals"?
- His monitor check out?
- Of course it does.
Damn it!
Looks like I just got fed
a bowl of malarkey.
We got 'em sir. Pym
and Van Dyne are in custody.
Seriously? Yes!
Oh, I'm sorry, Scott.
They're your friends.
That's insensitive.
I just really needed a win,
you know?
Anyway, I'll be back later
for the official end
of your sentence!
Sorry for misjudging you, pal!
You should feel great
about yourself!
What is it?
We have a man down.
And Pym's lab is gone.
Hey.
Thanks for covering for me.
Sure.
So...
how long
have you been Ant-Man again?
Not long.
It just sort of happened.
I'm sorry for lying to you...
and I'm sorry
for risking everything.
Daddy, it's okay.
It's not.
I do some dumb things...
and the people that I love
the most pay the price.
Mainly you.
Trying to help people
isn't dumb.
I screw it up
just about every time.
So, maybe you just need
someone watching your back...
like a partner.
Well, she's made it clear
that's about the last thing
she wants.
Who?
Hope.
Wait, who did you think?
Me.
You?
Don't laugh.
I'd be a great partner.
Aw, peanut.
Aw. You would be awesome.
And if I let you...
I would be a terrible dad.
Fine.
Then have Hope be
your partner. She's smart.
She reminds me of you.
You gonna go help her?
I think you should help her.
I wish I could...
but I don't know how I could
help her without hurting you.
You can do it.
You can do anything.
You are the world's
greatest grandma.
Agent Woo will see you
in an hour.
An hour?
We don't have an hour.
Oh, you got
somewhere else to be?
Oh, now, that's my girl.
All right, what's our plan?
To shrink that wall.
It looks load-bearing.
The ceiling could collapse.
Then we run like hell.
Now, I estimate 15-20 agents
on the floor.
Roughly five times that
in the building at large.
They're all heavily armed.
Not great odds.
You got any better ideas?
Nope.
And I'm not giving up on Mom.
She'd be so proud of you.
Okay.
One...
two...
Scott?
What're you two
just standing around for?
We gotta go find that lab.
What about me?
Perfect.
Hurry up and get dressed.
We don't have much time.
Okay, now what?
You're asking me?
Get in!
Hi.
Uh, excuse me. Are we planning
on leaving soon...
or are you two gonna keep
staring at each other...
until they start shooting at us?
Yeah.
- Hey, Burch.
- Yeah.
Yeah, they're out.
I'm on my way.
Her suit is missing,
and so is the van.
How could this happen?
I mean, what the dickens?
Thank you.
You're welcome.
So, uh, how do we find the lab?
After we lost it
the first time...
I put on a new tracker...
of sorts.
That'll work.
Is it ready or not?
We can begin
the extraction process.
Listen, Ava.
This whole thing
could be very dangerous.
Maybe we should...
Maybe we should what? Wait?
I've got days until I'm dead.
We're doing this, Bill. Now.
Energy readings show they
have not used the tunnel yet.
We don't have much time before
Mom's location shifts,
and we lose her.
Yeah, and we have
a lot to do before then.
You know,
my pep-pep always said,
"If you want to do something
right, you make a list."
So, we should do that.
One, we have to break
into that lab.
Two, we have to kick out
Foster and Ghost.
Three, we're gonna
have to fight Ghost.
That seems like it should be
part of two. 2-A, all right?
Let's call it 2-A.
Fight Ghost. 2-A.
Oh, also, we have to make sure
that the lab
is fully grown
for you to come back.
Otherwise, we're screwed.
Scott!
You want me to start again?
I'll start again...
I'm going to dive.
The only chance we got is if
the two of you are out here...
together, protecting the tunnel.
Let me do this, Hope. Please.
Let me get her.
I think he's right.
"Whassup?"
You don't remember, uh,
that beloved commercial?
"Whassup?"
I had him follow us.
I thought we could use
some help.
All right.
I'm in position.
The ants are headed in.
Copy that.
Keep your eyes peeled, Scotty.
- Do you want Pez?
- No.
Cassie gave me this
for my birthday.
By the way, I love that suit!
Thanks, man.
I wish I had a suit.
I would even like a suit
with minimal powers, you know?
Or maybe even just a suit,
with no powers.
What is it?
Don't know.
It's them!
They can't be far.
All right, Hank. Hank?
Dad, what's your status?
Foster's taken care of.
Suiting up now.
I just wanted to save Ava.
She's facing death or
something far more terrible.
She's afraid.
I'll help you find a cure
when I get back.
I promise.
Together, we'll figure
something out.
Good luck, Hank.
Thanks, Bill.
Now, I'm gonna need you
to step back.
Time remaining, 15 minutes.
Hank's in, Scott.
Any sign of her?
No, nothing yet.
Ava!
Call off the ants, Scott.
Oh, boy!
Can I get a status report?
'Cause I got some
serious Ghost problems here!
Ready to dive.
- In case I don't make it...
- Don't.
Don't say that.
I can't lose you, too.
I love you, Hope.
Guys,
everything's bad over here.
Now.
Misdirection.
One of the first things
they teach you
at Online Close-up
Magic University.
No!
Plan worked.
We got it, Scotty!
Meet us at the rendezvous point.
Okay, on my way!
Oh, no.
Really?
This guy again?
Who?
I told you
our business wasn't over.
Change of plans.
Hang on.
I want that lab, boys,
whatever it takes.
Hold on.
That undercarriage is filthy!
Oh, they got bigger problems.
Hope, what're you doing?
You're heading away
from the rendezvous point!
Don't worry,
I'm taking these guys
on the scenic route.
Wait, what're you... Oh.
Oh, my God! Oh, my God!
We're gonna die!
Signal lost.
What the hell
are they doing up there?
Recalibrating.
You never said
it was so beautiful, Scott.
Recalibrating.
Okay, any time now.
- Recalibrating.
- Come on.
Signal restored.
Bikes, it's all you.
- Take the wheel.
- What? Wait! Whoa.
Well, the 60's were fun,
but now I'm paying for it.
Be careful up there!
Hey, give me a break!
I haven't driven in two years!
Oh, you got pezed!
Up here!
Oh, that's not good.
Hope!
- No!
There it is, right there.
Get the lab!
I've got her.
Westbound on Fremont.
Hope! Wait!
Hey, what about me?
We got you now, Ava!
Whoa! Oh!
Not again!
Piece of junk!
Ah! Yes!
Go, go, go, go, go!
Burch got the lab.
I'm going after him.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Work in progress, my ass...
Scott, where are you?
I've got Burch in my sights.
Hurry!
I'm coming,
I'm coming, I'm coming!
We're running out of time.
Warning,
approaching quantum void.
I'm coming to you, honey.
Guys.
Don't you need the remote
to the lab? I just found it.
We can't grow
the lab without it.
Get it to us fast.
Yeah, but the van is busted.
Use the Hot Wheels Rally case.
What?
I love you, Dr. Pym.
The remote!
We're missing the remote!
You gotta check the van!
Huh?
Awesome!
Hey, I'm going down Pacific.
Burch's boys are all over me.
I'm on my way.
Right. I'll get the lab.
Hi.
Oh, that's badass!
Nice.
Doink!
Come here, you little weasel!
No, you don't!
I guess maybe you do.
Come on!
Anyone see a Southern
gentleman carrying a building?
How'd he even have time
to buy a ticket?
Would you just one time,
please work!
Yes!
All right, I need help.
Oh. Sorry. Ah...
Somebody!
Hey! Come on, man!
Not cool!
Murderers!
Yes, yes, yes, yes!
I'm gonna call you
Ant-onio Banderas!
You're a badass!
Yes!
No, no, no!
Ant-onio!
Our friends, the humpbacks,
dip in here
to the San Francisco Bay...
for a little leisure
and a little breeding.
Listen, Uzman...
And perhaps they're down below
as we speak, doing the nasty.
Just meet me at the waterfront.
In three hours.
Oh, folks.
We've barely left the dock...
but it looks like
we got some company.
Look. Right there.
Do you see it, folks?
There it is.
There's a breach.
What the...?
Hi. Sorry. Hi.
It's okay. It's okay!
Sorry, I know I'm not a whale.
This will just take a second.
Hey! That doesn't belong
to you!
No, no! No, no!
You're embarrassing yourself now
Come on. Let go.
Thank you.
I'll take this now.
It melts your mind.
A message in your head.
I had a dream.
Daddy?
Where's Mommy?
It's where I hid
every time that we played.
I love you, Hank.
Daddy?
Dad?
What's going on?
Why haven't you found Mom?
You look lost, Hank.
Are you all right?
Still think you have
all the answers, Hank?
It's me.
I'm so sorry...
it took so long.
No.
You're here now.
Let's go home.
I thought I was gone.
But that energy
from your hands...
how did you do that?
I'm not the same woman I was
30 years ago, Henry.
This place...
it changes you.
Adaptation is part of it,
but some of it is...
evolution.
Lab coordinates not found.
Do not ascend.
I should probably tell you
what we're dealing with
up there.
I got the lab. I got the lab.
Move.
Move!
Get out of the way.
Let's go.
No one here appears
to be sure what this is.
It's gotta be 80-85 feet tall.
Get out of the way!
I got the lab.
The air feels chunky.
Oh, no. He's too big.
Scotty!
Scott!
I'm gonna go to sleep.
I'm just gonna go to sleep now
for five minutes.
I just need five minutes.
Five minutes!
You get the lab somewhere safe.
- Scott's air won't last.
- Okay.
Move!
Move! Move!
No, wait!
Lab at full scale.
They did it.
Ready to ascend.
Let's go see our daughter.
Scott!
Scott, come on, wake up!
Come on.
Come on, where are you, Scott?
Gotcha.
Scott?
Hey.
Hey, Scotty!
Hope, come in.
Did you get crushed
by the building?
Where's the remote, Luis?
It's probably in there.
I don't have it.
I guess this is where we say...
Adios, amigo.
No, no, no, no!
Thanks, guys.
Ava?
Ava!
Almost ready for extraction.
Please, stop!
People are getting hurt!
Everything hurts.
Don't talk to me about pain!
What if Hank is right?
What if this process
kills Janet?
What, you're worried about her?
All I'm saying is that she is
a brilliant scientist.
She may be able to help.
Oh, she will help.
Right now!
And if she dies, she dies!
No, no. I'm sorry,
we can't do this.
We have to find another way.
This is the way.
Janet!
She started the extraction.
She's gonna tear Mom apart.
No!
Hope!
Are you okay?
Mom?
Oh, my God.
We found you.
I missed you so much.
I missed you too, Jellybean.
It's okay.
I'm here now.
We have time.
No more last-minute
business trips, okay?
I promise.
No, it's okay!
It's all right.
Just don't worry about me.
- I'll be fine.
- Dad.
Scott.
Miss Van Dyne.
It's nice to...
Well, I guess we've already met.
Yeah. I guess we have.
Wait.
Your pain.
I can feel it.
It hurts.
It always hurts.
I'm sorry.
I think I can help you.
Did you know she could do that?
It's okay.
Guys, the cops are coming!
Whoa.
The cops are coming.
Like, all of 'em!
- I gotta go.
- We gotta go!
What about them?
Hands in the air!
- No! We are going to our jobs.
- No.
You see, we see these guys.
They trying to shoot people.
So we apprehended them.
For you. You're welcome.
We traffic in stolen technology.
And we have killed many,
many people.
Uh, he's in charge.
That's true, I am.
I've also committed
numerous health code
violations in my restaurant.
Some of them would shock you.
It is truth serum.
We gotta get outta here.
Fast.
I have an idea.
Giant figure, now spotted
at the intersection of
Broadway and Laguna.
All units move in.
Go, go!
There he is!
It's over, Scotty!
I'm sorry, but we got you, man!
Come on.
It's the end of the line, pal.
There's nowhere to hide.
Just pull off that Band-Aid!
You lost! It's okay!
Damn it, Scotty,
reduce yourself!
Magic.
Damn it!
Get to Lang's, now!
Well done, honey.
Let's go!
Leave me here.
We can make it.
You said it yourself.
I've hurt people.
But you haven't.
Go. Please!
We can make it, Ava.
Bill...
I'm not leaving you.
Oh, hey, guys.
Are my two years up already?
What's it like out there?
Huh? I mean,
do people still dance?
Are food trucks still a thing?
Well, you got away with it
this time, Scott...
but, uh,
I'll be seeing you again.
Where?
Huh?
Where will you be
seeing me again?
Like, in general...
The next time
you do something bad,
- I'll be there to catch you...
- Oh.
You'll be watching...
I thought you were
inviting me somewhere.
Why would I do that?
That's what I was wondering,
why would you do that?
Like a party, or like,
dinner or something?
I don't know. I thought you
planned the evening.
I meant, "I'll arrest you
later, again."
Of course,
that would be strange.
- Take it easy, Jimmy.
- Okay.
Did you want to grab dinner,
or something?
I mean, because I'm free...
Yeah. Come on.
You ready?
Yeah!
- Hi.
- Hi. Hi.
Oh!
Yes, that was us.
How can I help you?
X-Con Security.
Mr. Karapetyan?
Yeah, you saw that?
It would be an honor to be
in business with you as well.
I'll see you Thursday,
9:00 AM. Okay.
Yeah!
That's how you close a deal!
This is awesome.
So, Cassie...
what do you want to be
when you grow up?
I wanna help people...
like my dad.
Really?
I wanted to be his partner.
But he said he wants you.
Is that so?
Daddy!
Whoa! Hold on.
Move, get outta here!
Scott, don't, don't, don't!
Ow.
Oh, gross!
Ugh. I hate that moth dust!
Go! Shoo! Shoo!
I used to be
a respected scientist.
I had my name
on the sides of buildings.
Now, I got this.
Well, you wanted
a smaller quantum tunnel.
This is... smaller.
Oh. Sorry. My bad.
Ah, I think it has flair.
All right. Control's online.
The collection unit activates
when you decouple it.
It should automatically
start absorbing
quantum healing particles.
Also, make sure you stay
out of the tardigrade fields.
They're cute,
but they'll eat you.
And don't get sucked
into a time vortex.
We won't be able to save you.
Okay.
Going subatomic in five...
four...
three...
two...
one.
All right, Scott,
this is a mic check.
Mic check, one, two.
One, two.
How's everybody doing tonight
in the quantum realm?
Scott, we read you.
I just wanna make sure.
Okay.
Healing particles secured
for our new Ghost friend.
Great.
Preparing for re-entry in...
five, four, three...
Hello?
Ha, ha. Very funny.
Hank, quit screwing around.
You told me yourself
not to screw around.
Hank?
Hope?
Janet.
Guys.
Okay, seriously,
don't joke around.
Bring me up, let's go.
Guys!
Modify by Blue-Bird™